http://xenogere.com/about/site/privacy-policy/

Introduction
I take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using my web site.  This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (hereafter referred to as “Data”) that may be collected during your use of this site.  This Policy does not apply to other entities that I do not own or control or persons that are not directly employed by me, acting as agents for me, or within my direct control.  Please take the time to read my Terms of Use as well.
1. Collection of Data
This site’s comment process requires only a valid e-mail address and a unique user ID.  Please note that your user name and any other content that you submit on this site may appear for others to see.  Like many web sites, xenogere may also automatically receive general information that is contained in the server log files such as your IP address and cookie information.
2. Use of Data
I may use Data to customize and improve your user experience while visiting this site.  I will take all steps available to ensure that your Data is never provided to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) I obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an Application Service Provider; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (v) I find that your use of my site violates this Policy, my Terms of Service, the law, my personable sensibilities and/or tastes, other usage guidelines in place now or enacted at a later date by me, or as deemed reasonably necessary by me to protect my legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the Data in the same manner as I set forth in this Policy (no, not likely, but always cover your assets [CYA]).  In the event you choose to use links that appear on this site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.
3. Cookies
Like many web sites, I set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings.  Although you can disallow/disable cookies for this site, you will simply be making your experience here less enjoyable.
4. Children
This site does not contain adult material, but it may from time to time host lively conversations and debates among mature audience members.
5. Editing or Deleting Your Account Information
I provide you with the ability to edit your user account information when submitting comments.  Content or other data that you may have provided to me, such as comments and news submissions, may continue to remain on this site at my discretion even though you no longer participate.  Please see my Terms of Use for more information.
6. Changes to this Privacy Policy
I may make changes to this Policy from time to time and at my sole discretion.  I will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on the site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to me that is contained within your user settings.
7. NO GUARANTEES
While this Privacy Policy states my standards for maintenance of Data and I will put forth every effort to enforce and meet them, I am not in a position to guarantee these standards.  There may be factors beyond my control that may result in the disclosure of Data (although I will do more than my best to ensure that doesn’t happen).  As a consequence, I disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.
8. Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Policy or my web site, please feel free to contact me.
a life in progress
About Me My name is Jason M Hogle.  I'm a friend, son, brother, writer, photographer, scientist, naturalist, mathematician, conservationist, poet, technology nut, and many other things.  I consider myself a Renaissance man.  I have a passion for learning.  I also have a passion for living.  What you see here is who I am, from my triumphs to my tribulations and everything that fills the space betwixt the two.  If you're still curious, read more about me.
Find Me OnFeatured Posts You might never see it again: When getting lost helps you find something beautiful and rare.
Baket: After years of befriending a predator.
Evening stroll: Anthropomorphizing an encounter with a pair of wood ducks.
Of serpentine surprises: Living in Texas means being mindful of snakes when the weather is warm.
Some comfort here: Thoughts on life, death and impermanence when a loved one faces a serious illness.
Recent Comments Clive Hicks-Jenkins: Too long since I’ve left a comment here. (Life gets so...
Dianna: Just found a dead one in crystal river Florida.
Alican Gunes: Not sure if you still check this place but I’ve a confession to...
Charlie: An old German proverb says, “God made the bee, but the devil made the...
Scott: Jason: When you entitled your post “She was Daddy’s girl”...
Janice Denham: My deepest sympathies. It’s never easy to lose a fur baby. RIP...
Jain: What a beautiful girl. I’m so sorry.
Harold Vance: Awesome tribute!
Connie: You are in my mind and memory and feel like family just from your stories you...
joshwlwgrvScott: It’s good to hear from you again. To put things bluntly, I...
Categories The Kids
Kako
al-Zill
Past Members:
Past Members:
Past Members:
